{
    "id": "d602ac6dfd034152b0eb2925b7b51b17",
    "title": "Review: Simple present tense",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ff3adfa7c25b4b4fb12208bf77eb5e2c",
            "title": "Simple Present Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When .................................... you get up in the morning?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ............................................ up at six o’clock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "gets"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .............................................. breakfast at 9 am.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................................. science at a private school.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "teach",
                        "teaches"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Jane ............................................ up at five o’clock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "gets"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Vicky ............................................. at a bank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "works"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ........................................... a six figure salary.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "earn",
                        "earns"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .......................................... a beauty parlor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "run",
                        "runs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You .............................................. well",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sing",
                        "sings"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ............................................. at bank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "works"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}